Episode 2
Where'd a Jaggy go?
Don't tell me he's sleeping in.
We have an escaped inmate!
Hunt out, use this kid and capture him!
Wado?!
One dream, one wish.
If you want it, gotta go over the top.
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no.
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you.
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're close to
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way.
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day.
Then make sure your only
thought you have is.
Yes, I can.
As you're on your way,
marks maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead at new horizons in view.
Shining brightly, oh, who
knows what's waiting for you.
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
Over the top.
Reliquity lost that round, huh?
And Mama as well.
She could be anywhere
after falling like that.
If we try climbing the waterfall.
He will just kick us down again.
That was one hell of a tumble!
I can't believe we
survived without a scratch.
It's a miracle that Chanta
landed right side off.
So, we're just supposed to wait?
I'm afraid so.
If any of us power users fall off
the ship, we'll be as good as dead.
Hold on!
You think that's what happened to Mama?
I wouldn't worry.
I checked Mama's Vivre card.
Unfortunately, it says she's
still among the Lickety Living.
So she didn't drown?
That's awesome!
But there's just water down there.
Where'd she go?
Good point.
That probably means the
Beast Pirates hauled her
up from the sea and
locked her away somewhere.
That complicates things.
What do you think they'll do?
Mom and Kaido were
crewmates many years ago.
But since they're both emperors now, they're
only interested in coming out on top.
In other words, they'll kill her for sure.
Then what's gonna happen to us?
The era of the big mom pirates will end.
Because they'll become the Pharaoh
Sparrow Pirates, of course.
Hold on.
Is that some kind of joke?
Because the next captain
should obviously be Katakuri.
But our crew values seniority.
Quality is what we need.
The eldest son should be the
Lickety Leader, you fool.
You are a fool.
I'll do it. Don't cut it out.
Mama won't die so easily.
She's not some mere commoner.
She'll keep fighting.
Who is Big Mom? A friend.
She's a strong lady from overseas.
Mom, ma-ma-ma-ma.
This shark-a-dile is so tame and
sweet, it even lets us run on its back.
Yeah, after you pounded
it on the head twice.
Wait, but why are you going
into Udon with this woman?
Nothing you're saying
makes a bit of sense to me.
I told you she's real strong,
so she'll help us save Big Bro.
This is making my head spin.
Just come back for now, please.
Then we can work all of this out.
Sir Kin'emon has left me with a mission.
I was to guard Lord Momonosuke in his
absence, as if my life depended on it.
Don't you worry.
I got this.
On my honor as a kunoichi, I vow that
no harm will come to the young lord.
What honor?
You've barely even started your training.
You can't even protect yourself.
Stop being ridiculous and return home before
something bad happens to you yet again.
Sir Hitetsu, I'm afraid
we're already on our way.
Well, turn back. I beg of you.
Be reasonable, Lady Okiku. Take care.
Come and see you for me.
Bye. Da-lick.
There's something you just said.
The name Big Mom sounds
awfully familiar to me.
Who could that be?
Never mind, Olene.
Your friends were so nice.
I had fun in Okobore town.
They're all so generous.
They don't know who I am.
I don't know who I am.
But they welcomed me like a guest and
even gave me a sweet treat to eat.
Her talking hat hasn't said a single word.
Does that mean it's lost its memory, too?
It's all coming back to me now.
The flavor of that sweet
soup melting in my mouth.
Don't look at me!
I can't help it, Topper-Abon.
You're so cute and sweet,
I could just eat you up.
How dare you! I'm not food!
You're working hard, Momo. I'm impressed.
I must stay sharp.
I am at the center of
this conflict, after all.
Tsunachi!
I'm sorry.
Most inconsiderate of me.
By the way, what's that thing you
say when you swing your sword?
Tsunachi or something, it sounds like?
That's correct.
It is a word that fills you with energy,
that's
quite enough,
both of you.
What's the matter?
Where did you learn such a word?
It's what they yell in sword fights.
Overseas, Zoro Giri taught it to me.
He says it's a good luck word to.
uplift your spirit when
your courage falters.
Then I forbid you to
say it. What? But why?
Perhaps it's merely a coincidence,
but the same word was once
used in an old Kuri dialect.
It's not appropriate for a person
of your standing to say. Why?
What harm does it do?
No.
But it gives you energy
and I think it's me.
I'm afraid no means no.
I'm positively famished.
Tell me we've made it
to Udon and I can eat.
I could really use a snack, you know.
Don't drool and talk about
snacks when you look at me!
I'm sorry, Oline, but I'm afraid we
still have quite a long way to go.
Oh, surely not!
I'll show you a rough
map of the land of Wano.
As you can see, we have six regions, each
with a different climate than the next.
They're divided by a river that
stretches across the entire island.
colored rice a secret message from
shinobu no doubt wait at the dried up well
that seems convenient
enough i am relieved to find
you in good health though
your pursuers must have been
persistent indeed if you fled
all the way here to ringo
but rest assured Orochi's
men will not follow this far.
I'm still shocked that
they would kill Komurasaki.
She was quite beloved. Yes.
The incident has thrown the
flower capital into an uproar.
It's sick.
She wasn't a threat to anyone.
But the second she stood up to
Orochi, they cut her right down.
Samurai, you're scary.
The man who killed her is a Yakuza
boss known as Napping Kyoshiro.
Kyoshiro?
The name is not familiar to me.
Though I am quite familiar with the most
famous Yakuza boss from 20 years ago.
He was called Hiogoro the Flower.
A rather extravagant name, but I like it.
Times have changed.
Hiogoro was a man of
honor who helped the weak.
He would never have
done such a cruel thing.
A shame he wasn't there.
It sounds like this Kyoshiro fellow
is quite the loathsome beast!
In that case, perhaps we shouldn't have
taken Otoko back to his pleasure hall.
Surely what he did was
just a show of loyalty.
You'd think he would go out of his way to
kill a child over a minor
infraction like that?
Well, he killed the Oiron who worked
for him, and she was a superstar.
It worries me.
We should check on her. Let's go back.
Don't catch a cold.
That's so much better.
Thank you, Shinobu.
Here's a thought.
If we're headed back to the capital,
let's have a nice warm soak in one of
their bathhouses to rest our weary bones.
I'm sold.
I can't wait. I agree.
It'll be a nice change of pace.
We'll need disguises.
Orochi controls every
aspect of the capital.
In other words, that applies to bath
water just as well as drinking water.
One question first.
Robi, perchance were you able to
collect any valuable information?
I'm afraid not.
Though I'll share my meager scraps.
I know what time Orochi will
wake up on the day of the battle.
I know what offerings they will
take with them to Onigashima.
I know Kaido's favorite food
and his crew's hierarchy.
And the number of soldiers
and weapons that...
That's meager?
By the way, I happened upon a poneglyph.
Alas, it wasn't a red one, though. Really?
You're two for two on
finding those, Bonkichi.
It was in a basement room
with a reinforced door.
An odd place full of wooden dolls.
There should be a road poneglyph
here, but if it's not in the castle,
we can assume it's on Onigashima.
Kaido's Island, huh?
Splendid.
We've acquired a treasure
Traffy of information.
The mission was a resounding success.
I thank you all.
To have such reliable
allies is truly a gift.
Since all that's settled, let's go.
We'll have a nice healing bath
and also see some panties, OK?
You'll stand out and
you're a pervert! What?
Breaking news!
Everyone's favorite Oiran, Komurasaki, met
a terrible fate at the Shogun's Banquet.
There was a big disagreement
and Kyoshiro cut her right down.
No lie!
Find out more right here! Don't be shy!
Komurasaki!
Don't you think you're
being a bit dramatic?
You only saw her once.
The whole world should mourn
the death of a beauty like her.
Seems the funeral's tomorrow.
You're heartless, all of you!
My raid suit?
You don't think Odobee and
the others got caught, do you?
I'm worried.
Do you think I should try
to contact them by smell?
What do you think, Sanji?
I know where to use this power.
I'll go to the women's bath.
It's my dream.
Hey, Sanji!
So much skin.
Right, whatever Usopp just said.
By the way, Traffy, is there
anything about Udon in the paper?
About Lufitaro, maybe?
Bet there is.
If he hasn't gone on a rampage
yet, it's only a matter of time.
I hope you're right.
I just can't wait to see him.
No article on Straw Hat, sorry.
Eustass, that dirty rat is here? Dirty?
Is he sneaking to the bath before me?
I mean, that's wild.
I didn't know he was in 102.
He's been working with Hawkins,
so when I saw him, I should have guessed
his partner would be here as well.
Or ex-partner, since it says here
he escaped from the prison in Udon.
Then just him, though!
So Luffy is still locked up?
Yeah, and this is going to make it
even harder for him to break out.
Okay, but you think they
have nice bathhouses there?
Shut up!
Enough about that!
You're not listening at all, are you?
Come here, you idiot!
Wait, guys, hold on!
I'm getting worried.
My crew went scouting, but
they haven't come back yet.
We've had enough trouble.
Can't something go right for once?
What is that?
Hey, punk!
Listen up.
I got a question for you.
Yeah, I would.
As I'm sure you've heard,
Eustass Kid has escaped.
I'm willing to bet you
know something about that.
Maybe you even helped him?
It stinks!
This is truly a gift.
I haven't eaten this much in ages.
I'm overwhelmed with gratitude.
I eat this food with a grateful
stomach and a heart full of love.
Hey, old man!
You wanna share some
of those with me? Duh!
Looks like you're having
a feast over there.
You sticking up for your pal,
kind of a coincidence that kid
disappears right after you got sent here.
I saw you chatting it up; we all did.
You're really grossing me out, oh
yeah, well learn to deal with it.
Because as long as you've
got those cuffs on,
you ain't doing crap—it's
only a matter of time before.
before your pal gets caught.
As it turns out, he didn't think
things through before he bailed.
That is to say, he still has the
C-prism stone cuffs on. Too bad.
We'll round him up in no
time and make him p-p-p-pay.
I'm telling you, your spit
stings cut it out. Oh, yeah?
Just sounds like you're
picking a fight with me.
OK, how about I go over the rules again?
For the first events, both
your arms will be cut off.
For the second events,
we chop off your legs.
And if you're naughty a third
time, then you'll die, understand?
So mind your manners, because if you
screw with me, you're dead, dead, dead!
He's just a poor old man.
You're going to kill him.
Please have mercy!
Surely you hard-working individuals
wouldn't tolerate a cheater like that!
Rules are rules.
If someone can't follow them, then
they forfeit their right to live.
Only fair, right?
If you can't work, then you should
step aside and starve to death.
It's the polite thing
to do, you understand.
So stop being rude, old man. Huh?
Hey, are you trying to crawl away from me?
Pathetic.
You can't even stand up straight.
So how the hell did you
get all these food tickets?
Who gave them to you?
Did you steal them?
My dumplings.
I can't lose them.
My precious dumplings.
Greedy, old piece of crap.
Hey!
They're so delicious!
You're stuffing them in
your mouth, aren't you?
You have no right to eat anything!
Do you hear me, you old fart?
You didn't earn a damn
bite! Spit them out!
Spit them out, you bastard!
I'll never spit them out.
These were a gift from my
savior, Mr. Straw Hatman.
I will never, ever let them go to waste.
You see?
Now let that be a lesson to you.
Why would you do this?
He broke the rules.
And the same will happen to you
if you don't fix that attitude.
Better keep that in mind.
Now spit it out!
The dumplings and the name of the
idiot who gave you those tickets!
I ate them!
If you're trying to piss me off,
then you've done a fine job, old man.
Who gave you the food tickets?
Who's breaking the rules?
You're just some punk!
But the person who gave me
those tickets is a man of honor.
He protects the weak from the mighty.
I must meet that chivalry with my
own, lest I be disgraced before him.
Now, kill me!
Meeting a man like that made
me think of bygone days.
Back then, they called
me Hyogoro the Flower.
After so long, my stomach is full
and my heart is filled with joy.
This is a land of samurai.
There used to be a bunch of men like him.
Rich in courage and pride.
And then you bastards killed them all!
Hey, Lufitaro, stop!
I've heard enough of you
for a lifetime You know
what happens when you
talk back to the guards?
Then kill me, you damn thug!
What did you say?
You want to try that again?
I said you're a damn thug, you bastard!
All you know is violence, you
don't have an ounce of pride!
Is that what you wanted to hear?
But in the end,
you conquered us because we lost our
spines and forgot what we were made of!
All right, old man, have it your way.
I'll smash your skull then!
Stop it!
You can't hit a guard!
They're gonna execute you!
Luffy Tyro! Hey! Hold that!
No! Stay back! You can't!
You'll die!
I don't believe it.
Please stop.
I've had enough.
I'm all spent.
I can't.
General type, who go?
Whoever attacks one of the
guards will be executed.
immediately.
And we all saw it this time.
Can't talk your way out of this.
Let's kill him.
No more mercy. Kill him.
General Solitaire, the keys have been
stolen. Monkey?
Someone made off with the keys
to the C-PRISM stone cuffs.
What are you doing, you fools?
Did anyone see who did it?
I don't know, it was some guy
with a freakishly huge head!
He told me I dropped the key that
had me replace it with a fake!
It's not my fault!
I have a thick shell, but he
taunted me about walking sideways!
He didn't even try to butter me up!
Useless!
I ought to make you into a bisque!
Oh crap!
Monkey!
He must be in the tower!
Search high and low in the attic too!
I have fulfilled my duty
as a ninja splendidly.
Now I must simply deliver the
keys. Onward! He's here. Hey, you!
A mirage?
Oh, a shooter!
If only I could have finished sooner.
Pardon the wait, Sir
LuffyTaro, but I'm coming!
Your freedom is close at hand!
And now, a stealthy departure. Beep!
Queen, Queen, Queen.
It's Master Queen.
Queen, Queen.
Queen! Queen! Queen! Queen!
Master Queen!
Elite performer has arrived!
Open the game!
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
Kill!
Kill! Kill!
Kill! Kill! Kill!
Kill Why is it so noisy in
there? Kill Em! Kill Em! Kill Em!
Kill Em!
He was so brave, but now
there's nothing he can do.
I won't forget you Louvetaro!
I swear, this is it for Omen! You too!
You did great, Mrs. Starhat.
You should be proud.
Cut it out.
This isn't over.
We'll both be free.
Don't resist. It's no use.
You can't win with those cuffs on anyway.
Might as well make it quick.
If you want to fight, then fight me.
Bring it on.
What the hell is going on with that guy?
Why is he able to fight
like that with the cuffs on?
We followed regulations.
So just like all the
other powered prisoners,
he should be just strong enough to work.
That's to say, he's only about
as tough as a regular schmuck.
Are you saying I'm weaker than
a regular schmuck? No, sir.
That's not what I meant.
He's running out of breath.
Warden!
The Sea Prism Stone is doing its job.
But the man has resolve.
He's pushing through it!
I'm the Warden here.
And I don't like having you violate
the laws of physics in my prison.
This place has been great training for me.
By the time I get these things off, I
know I'm going to be stronger than before.
You're working hard for the future.
But in reality, you have none.
I can use a good sparring
partner, why not?
Let's do this!
You're rather cocky,
aren't you? Very well.
This'll put you in your place.
Elephant smart chew!
Now sneeze!
That looked bad, Mr. Straw Hat.
Tell me you're still alive.
Damn it.
He's strong.
Babanuki, sir.
Master Queen arrived a moment ago.
Why didn't you tell me?
What am I supposed to do now?
Move it, boy.
If Queen already started his show
and I get there late, you're dead!
I'm sorry! Damn it!
I can't even use my Haki!
Oh, my sweet Komurasaki.
You're so cute.
Oh, I'm getting pumped!
You're too good for oral jeep, baby.
Oh, so even is combo.
Right, it's showtime.
We'll stop by the brothel
once I'm done here.
Roger, Zach!
Don't you think we should tell
him that Komorosaki's dead?
He'll kill us for sure, man.
Let someone else do it.
Time to party.
Not gonna lose no weight,
just more to appreciate I got enough fans
attracted to my fuck
I look round as a ball,
but all of this is muscle,
y 'all These bomb-ass moves
of mine are powered by my fuck
Sorry to keep you waiting,
you pieces of shit
Climb up. Okay.
All right.
Lay it on me one by one.
What's got to be in your bonnet today?
Baba Nuki's top three pains in my ass.
And...
And go!
Number three.
Eustass Kidd has escaped from the camp.
Wado?
Hm.
Number two.
The keys to the sea prism stone
handcuffs have been stolen.
Wado? Mm-mm-mm.
Emmy number one.
Straw Hat Luffy's running wild.
He's over there.
Wado?
Stop!
Then chase him!
Come on, man!
Don't you worry a bit, friends.
This house is empty.
You're free to use it as much as you like.
If you're pals with Zoro Shura, then that
makes the two of you Aqua in my book.
Well, thanks.
Oh, it's hardly worth thanking me for.
Empty houses are opening up left and right,
Because people keep starving to death.
You fellas sure are lucky.
I'm not seeing the joke here.
I guess he just likes to laugh.
Well, when you're this hungry,
you either laugh or you cry.
Anyway, bad timing, my friends.
You just missed Zorojuro.
Well, can you tell us
where he went? Sorry.
He dashed out the door before
I could ask where he was going.
Said his sword was stolen.
Should have seen his face.
Who knows how far the
poor man's gone by now.
Even if he did get his sword,
he'll never find his way back here.
Not this again.
By the way, shouldn't Blackleg
be with us right now, too? Huh?
Where did he run off to?
You're kidding me!
I know exactly where to use this power.
I'm gonna go to the women's bath.
This is my dream.
Okay, but you think they
have nice bathhouses there?
That moron!
We have to stop him!
So this is what baths are like here, huh?
The water's a bit too
hot for my taste, though.
People around here like to show off.
I'm sure they keep it this hot just so
they can say, is it chilly in here today?
Guess there are lots of things
about this place I don't get.
Is it too hot for you to get in?
It's not so bad after a while.
It would leave me feeling a
bit defenseless, I'm afraid.
What if an enemy showed up?
As cautious as a ninja,
a fine trait to have.
Since Order B and I are both magic users,
it's only natural that we're
wary when we take a bath.
But no need to worry.
We'll be safe here.
Her enemies might not
bother me, but they will.
Should I charge a viewing fee?
Seriously?
A mixed bath?
You sound awfully surprised.
I didn't think anything of it,
but perhaps mixed baths are
uncommon where you're from?
Well, you'll get used to it.
Naughty boys gawking at you
is nothing unusual in here.
Not that I can blame them.
It's only natural they'd
want a little peek at this.
Eat your hearts out, gentlemen!
There's no need to be shy!
Move! Move! Move!
Neen-ho! Bowcrusher!
Let's move on to the washing area.
After we've warmed up in the bath, we
have Sansa-kay wash our bags. Sansa-kay?
Who is that?
Huh?
Yo!
That's Sansa-kay.
A title we give to the experts who
scrub our backs at the bathhouse.
Why an octopus, though?
Since he has eight limbs, that
makes him a real pro at this.
Pretty handy, right? Damn it!
Kyoshiro creeps me out!
I can't get inside his head!
Well, you can't trust the Yakuza.
What are you talking
about, you young folks?
The Yakuza in this country
are allies to the common man!
Or they were back in my day, anyways.
Their old boss.
He was a great man named
Hyogoro, the flower.
Is that the person Kanjuro was
talking about before though I am
quite familiar with the most famous
yakuza boss from 20 years ago.
He was called hyogoro the flower.
Hyogoro was indeed a man
of courage and honor.
I wish he was with us.
The samurai would heed his call.
I'm certain of it to be honest.
I doubt we'll be able to recruit
5 000 troops without him.
500 may be the best we can do.
Wow.
Sounds like he was something else.
Indeed.
Twenty years ago, he was the most
influential man in the underworld.
He was always pulling strings behind
the scenes in the flower capital.
He won the respect of
the Yakuza bosses in all
the other regions of the
land of Wano as well.
Known for his chivalry and charisma,
he would protect those in
need when the law could not.
He was strong, too.
That was why even Lord
Odin looked up to him.
So is there a reason why
we can't recruit this guy?
Well, it's been over 20
years since he was in charge.
These days, no one knows where he is.
Most believe that he was killed by
Orochi when he refused to serve his clan.
Fukurokuju,
the leader of the Oniwa Banshu, once
supported the Kozuki clan alongside Hyogoro.
But he decided to take
the opposite path from
Hyogoro and pledges loyalty
to Orochi these days.
I worked for him when he first changed
sides, but I couldn't take it and ran away!
From that day forward.
I became their enemy
I see now.
So it's you
Highness you're still alive
you bewitching vixen you
seductress kunoichi That's
why that ninja knew you, huh?
How cool you're famous
Well, yes.
It is a shame, though.
I miss Yoguro, but he's nothing
more than a piece of history now.
How many times are you going
to make me say it, huh?
Just join our crew and Kaido
will pardon you for your crimes.
Trust me, you're not going to
get a better deal than this.
No way! You suck!
Oh, this is truly unfortunate timing.
So, Luffy, I have the key you need...
Bet this looks real familiar, Hyogoro.
If I recall, Kaido and Orochi wanted you
on their side pretty badly back in the day.
But now, the big fancy Yakuza boss is
nothing but a malnourished old fart.
Bet you'd wish you'd taken
that offer back then.
wait did he say hyogoro but that
old man's so tiny you could pick
him up with one hand my days are
past but please don't let mr.
Straw Hat it up like me
have mercy i beg of you
What to do?
Oh, wait a sec.
I got an idea.
This is going to be wild.
What should I do?
I can scarcely believe it.
You haven't changed a
bit since I last saw you.
Who is it?
Who gazes from the darkness?
It is I, old friend.
What of Lord Momonosuke?
Does he live?
He can't be!
Are you?
Kawamatsu!